Suin Lee

394 Sammon Ave, East York, ON M4J 2A8 | +1 (416) 272–9102 | <u>lilesooin@gmail.com</u>

Please check this link: portfolio link

Github: https://github.com/lilsooin, https://github.com/star1606

I have experience in successfully developing and launching products for various services such as shopping mall, dashcam, kiosks, and lawn financial service. I am very interested in improving the development culture and processes within companies. In fact, I have reduced development time by creating and applying modular projects. I have a keen interest in programming and enjoy learning about technology in my spare time, as well as discussing programming-related topics.

SKILLS

- **Programming**: Java, Kotlin, C#, Javascript
- Mobile Development: Android, Reactive Programming
- Web Development: JPA(ORM framework), QueryDSL, JSP, Mybatis, React
- Databases: Firebase, MySQL
- Frameworks: Spring boot, AOSP(Android Open Source Project)
- CI/CD: firebase app distribution
 Version Control: Git, GitHub, Gitlab
 Collaboration tool: Jira, Slack, Notion

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software engineer, Hyundai Telecom, Seoul, Republic of Korea

March 2023 - September 2023

- Played a role in controlling lighting, calling elevators, and activating the 'outing mode' via an Android application that manipulates home appliances.
- Implemented code using Reactive Programming with RxJava to understand and manage data stream easily.
- Developed an Excel program aimed at facilitating the easy insertion of configuration data and conducting seminars for educating newcomers.

Backend developer, Android developer, Weeds communications, Seoul, Republic of Korea

December 2020 - August 2022

- Contributed to API design and development, utilizing Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) techniques to create code that is easily reusable and maintainable within the Lawn Financial Service project.
- Developed a dashcam video player application integrating it with the dashcam device via hotspot, which implemented streaming videos, downloading videos, UDP server connectivity, and a library enabling pinch zoom within the layout view for enhanced user interaction.
- Modularized frequently used functionalities to create a common component library, thereby increasing development efficiency and significantly reducing development time during project progression.
- Enhanced both developer and user experiences by implementing Firebase app distribution and OAuth2 login authentication.
- Developed anonymous login, integrated Crashlytics and performed NoSQL-based database modelling for real-time DB and cloud storage within Firebase in the Kiosks project.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Technology, Centennial College

January 2024 –

Busan IT InstitutionMarch 2020 – September 2020

- Completed a 6-month programming boot camp, focusing on backend education.
- Developed various backend projects: blog project, game project and To-do project.

Busan, Republic of Korea

Busan, Republic of Korea

February 2012 – August 2019

Suin Lee

394 Sammon Ave, East York, ON M4J 2A8 Email. lilesooin@gmail.com / Mobile. +1 416-272-9102

September 7, 2024

Dear Principal Investigator:

Please consider my attached resume for the backend developer position at WIMTACH company. After reviewing the job description, I believe the position is an excellent match for my career, especially considering **+2 years** of software engineering experience in my home country, where I worked on various projects involving **backend development** and **android development**

I have experience in various projects from large corporation to agency so I can quickly adapt to new projects. I have been working at Hyundai which is Korean big company, where I developed control functions such as lighting, elevator, and, outing for smart home products. I also contributed to building Korea's first bank cloud server in collaboration with Hanwha Financial, a major corporation in South Korea, where I was responsible for entity design and API design in the common part for both customers and employees and implemented logging systems that recorded activity based on filters according to user permissions, capturing logs during login and API communication. Additionally, while collaborating with a startup company, I developed launch a shopping mall service, where I was responsible for implementing member information management, login and authentication, crew management, and community features.

Here is my portfolio link

Please check this link: portfolio link

I welcome the opportunity to meet you and discuss my qualification in greater detail. I am going to follow up with you to check on the status of my application. Thank you in advance for your consideration.

Sincerely,

Suin Lee